<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CSFoodForThought</string>

    <string name="chicken_pasta_bake_method">STEP 1
\nneat 2 tbsp of the oil in a pan over a medium heat and fry the onion gently for 10-12 mins. Add the garlic and chilli flakes and cook for 1 min. Tip in the tomatoes and sugar and season to taste. Simmer uncovered for 20 mins or until thickened, then stir through the mascarpone.

\n\nSTEP 2
\nHeat 1 tbsp of oil in a non-stick frying pan. Season the chicken and fry for 5-7 mins or until the chicken is cooked through.

\n\nSTEP 3
\nHeat the oven to 220C/200C fan/gas 7. Cook the penne following pack instructions. Drain and toss with the remaining oil. Tip the pasta into a medium sized ovenproof dish. Stir in the chicken and pour over the sauce. Top with the cheddar, mozzarella and parsley. Bake for 20 mins or until golden brown and bubbling.</string>

    <string name="tomato_soup_method">STEP 1
\nHeat the butter or oil in a large pan, then add the garlic and soften for a few minutes over a low heat. Add the sundried tomatoes, canned tomatoes, stock, sugar and seasoning, then bring to a simmer. Let the soup bubble for 10 mins until the tomatoes have broken down a little.
\n\nSTEP 2
\nWhizz with a stick blender, adding half the pot of soured cream as you go. Taste and adjust the seasoning – add more sugar if you need to. Serve in bowls with 1 tbsp or so of the pesto swirled on top, a little more soured cream and scatter with basil leaves.</string>

    <string name="sausage_roasted_veg_and_puy_lentils_one_pot_method">STEP 1
\nHeat grill to high. Put the sausages in a large roasting tin and grill for 8-10 mins until browning, then switch the oven on to 200C/180C fan/gas 6. Remove the tin from the oven and add the vegetables and garlic, then drizzle over the oil and toss in the paprika and some seasoning.
\n\nSTEP 2
\nRoast for 30-35 mins more until the sausages and veg are mostly tender, then stir through the lentils and vinegar. Return to the oven for 5 mins until everything is heated through. Squeeze the garlic cloves out of their skins and stir the garlic into the lentils, then season to taste, stir through the parsley and serve.</string>

    <string name="curry_method">STEP 1
\nHeat the oil in a flameproof casserole dish or large frying pan over a medium heat. Add the onion and a generous pinch of salt and fry for 8-10 mins, or until the onion has turned golden brown and sticky. Add the garlic and ginger, cooking for a further minute.

\n\nSTEP 2
\nChop the chicken into chunky 3cm pieces, add to the pan and fry for 5 mins before stirring through the spice paste and tomatoes, along with 250ml water. Bring to the boil, lower to a simmer and cook on a gentle heat uncovered for 25-30 mins or until rich and slightly reduced. Stir though the yogurt, coriander and ground almonds, season and serve with warm naan or fluffy basmati rice.</string>

    <string name="pancake_method">STEP 1
\nPut 100g plain flour, 2 large eggs, 300ml milk, 1 tbsp sunflower or vegetable oil and a pinch of salt into a bowl or large jug, then whisk to a smooth batter.
\n\nSTEP 2
\nSet aside for 30 mins to rest if you have time, or start cooking straight away.
\n\nSTEP 3
\nSet a medium frying pan or crêpe pan over a medium heat and carefully wipe it with some oiled kitchen paper.
\n\nSTEP 4
\nWhen hot, cook your pancakes for 1 min on each side until golden, keeping them warm in a low oven as you go.
\n\nSTEP 5
\nServe with lemon wedges and caster sugar, or your favourite filling. Once cold, you can layer the pancakes between baking parchment, then wrap in cling film and freeze for up to 2 months.</string>
</resources>